<root>
<kyero>
<feed_version>3</feed_version>
</kyero>
<property>
<id>498</id>
<date>2025-08-27 10:25:53</date>
<ref>624</ref>
<price>1150000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Villa ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>4</beds>
<baths>4</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>317</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/498/villa/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas in Finestrat Paradise Resort are situated on spacious plots from 527 m² to 688 m², with a total constructed area of 317.50 m². In addition, they have two open terraces of 28 m² and 8 m², as well as a 62 m² solarium to enjoy the wonderful weather and views. These exclusive villas offer 4 bedrooms and 4 bathrooms, as well as an underground parking area of 73 m² with capacity for 2 cars.&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas en Finestrat Paradise Resort se sitúan en amplias parcelas de 527 m² a 688 m², con una superficie construida total de 317,50 m². Además, cuentan con dos terrazas descubiertas de 28 m² y 8 m², así como un solárium de 62 m² para disfrutar del clima y las vistas. Estas exclusivas villas ofrecen 4 dormitorios y 4 baños, además de una zona de aparcamiento interior de 73 m² con capacidad para 2 coches.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De villa's liggen op kavels van 527 tot 688 m², met een totale bebouwde oppervlakte van 317,50 m². Ze beschikken over twee open terrassen van 28 m² en 8 m², en een solarium van 62 m². Deze exclusieve villa's hebben 4 slaapkamers en 4 badkamers, evenals een ondergrondse garage van ca 73 m² voor twee auto's.&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont situées sur des parcelles spacieuses de 527 m² à 688 m², avec une surface construite totale de 317,50 m². Elles disposent en outre de deux terrasses ouvertes de 28 m² et 8 m², ainsi que d'un solarium de 62 m² pour profiter du beau temps et de la vue. Ces villas exclusives offrent 4 chambres et 4 salles de bains, ainsi qu'un parking au sous-sol de 73 m² pour 2 voitures.&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort znajdują się na przestronnych działkach o powierzchni od 527 m² do 688 m², z łączną powierzchnią zabudowy wynoszącą 317,50 m². Ponadto posiadają dwa otwarte tarasy o powierzchni 28 m² i 8 m², a także solarium o powierzchni 62 m², idealne do cieszenia się doskonałą pogodą i widokami. Te ekskluzywne wille oferują 4 sypialnie i 4 łazienki, a także podziemny parking o powierzchni 73 m², mieszczący 2 samochody.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji. ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Garage</feature>
<feature>Garden</feature>
<feature>Private pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Solarium</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating throughout the property</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Solar panels</feature>
<feature>Pre-installation electric vehicle charging point</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27eruhq1bga160f15ft1be71r.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er9ubg4cb2au5iham1s.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er4nv13q3j1v1t4t137l23.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tuc23g8j4bvm17v6hpqng11g.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1qnb1ib61smeehf1koq24.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1d301t5n11oflb11iu41t.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27erca6rbl1sv38en8rm1u.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er10cn6pd1pbmrac103p22.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1qdq2oe1tek14851v811v.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1mgrk9k1nau1vir10em20.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1608dii16i11ldd7tu21.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27erm041rskfnspsg16eg25.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i7ds27er1nro1n8lfp5bv28jv26.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>500</id>
<date>2025-07-22 15:05:43</date>
<ref>625</ref>
<price>395000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>80</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/500/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The ground floor properties have generous private gardens ranging. These green areas offer direct access to the swimming pool and communal areas, creating a perfect space to relax and enjoy the surroundings to the full. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las viviendas en planta baja cuentan con generosos jardines privados. Estas áreas verdes ofrecen acceso directo a la piscina y a las zonas comunes, creando un espacio perfecto para relajarse y disfrutar al máximo del entorno. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De appartementen op de begane grond hebben een privétuin. Deze tuinen bieden directe toegang tot het zwembad en de gemeenschappelijke ruimtes, waardoor een ideale plek ontstaat om te ontspannen en van de omgeving te genieten.&amp;nbsp;Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen. Er is tevens een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les appartements du rez-de-chaussée disposent de généreux jardins privés. Ces espaces verts offrent un accès direct à la piscine et aux espaces communs, créant ainsi un endroit idéal pour se détendre et profiter pleinement de l'environnement. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ &#13;&#13; Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Nieruchomości na parterze posiadają przestronne prywatne ogrody. Te zielone przestrzenie zapewniają bezpośredni dostęp do basenu i stref wspólnych, tworząc idealne miejsce do relaksu i pełnego korzystania z otoczenia. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji. ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Garden</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i9md818u41o6eccv1t4q1r.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i9v8bc6a1k69an7136i1s.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu47db1b8i16n0125us15mhd1g.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i919h6jbn56q6m713561u.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i91hvbmvv162ck5cdi01t.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i9lqkps21i561e9noun21.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i9dpm15fmlvg1pjquln22.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i94l51do41odd1f5up1p23.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i91puc4bo3vitdbg2t24.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i91mlhsv02701tal1cu125.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i919q61lm7fit1eoe15uu26.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgh9i9m8kvr1v3h1me2u4p1v.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgnpmvh8kf361or9i6m4ej53.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fgnpmvk1v4ul1c6ui231i9m54.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>501</id>
<date>2025-04-25 10:25:41</date>
<ref>626</ref>
<price>565000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>3</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>103</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/501/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The ground floor properties have generous private gardens ranging. These green areas offer direct access to the swimming pool and communal areas, creating a perfect space to relax and enjoy the surroundings to the full.&amp;nbsp;Each apartment comes with two parking spaces and two storage rooms in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las viviendas en planta baja cuentan con generosos jardines privados. Estas áreas verdes ofrecen acceso directo a la piscina y a las zonas comunes, creando un espacio perfecto para relajarse y disfrutar al máximo del entorno. Cada apartamento viene con dos plazas de parking y dos trasteros en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De appartementen op de begane grond hebben een privétuin. Deze tuinen bieden directe toegang tot het zwembad en de gemeenschappelijke ruimtes, waardoor een ideale plek ontstaat om te ontspannen en van de omgeving te genieten. Twee&amp;nbsp;ondergrondse parkeerplaatsen&amp;nbsp;en twee bergingen zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen, alsook&amp;nbsp;een gemeenschappelijke&amp;nbsp;fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les appartements du rez-de-chaussée disposent de généreux jardins privés. Ces espaces verts offrent un accès direct à la piscine et aux espaces communs, créant ainsi un endroit idéal pour se détendre et profiter pleinement de l'environnement. Chaque appartement dispose de deux places de stationnement et de deux débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Nieruchomości na parterze posiadają przestronne prywatne ogrody. Te zielone przestrzenie zapewniają bezpośredni dostęp do basenu i stref wspólnych, tworząc idealne miejsce do relaksu i pełnego korzystania z otoczenia. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Garden</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu5ejh1edjnmh1uhotvv1rfo1g.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170b16111166f170b16114e.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170af8509866f170af850d5.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170b51e41766f170b51e454.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170b34939e66f170b3493ec.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170baaaee366f170baaaf20.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170bc7875766f170bc78794.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170be4705666f170be470be.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170c00f19066f170c00f1d9.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170c1d163866f170c1d1675.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170c39cad166f170c39cb0d.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170b6e3a2a66f170b6e3a69.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170c56907566f170c5690b1.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f170b8c3c9f66f170b8c3cd7.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>503</id>
<date>2025-06-27 11:06:18</date>
<ref>627</ref>
<price>375000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>80</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/503/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The apartments have 2 bedrooms and 2 bathrooms, all with spacious terraces to enjoy the fresh air, the views and the Mediterranean climate. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Los apartamentos ofrecen 2 dormitorios y 2 baños, todos con terrazas espaciosas para disfrutar del aire libre, las vistas y el clima mediterránea. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De appartementen bieden 2 slaapkamers en 2 badkamers, met ruime terrassen om te genieten van de frisse lucht, het uitzicht en het mediterrane klimaat. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen. , alsook een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les appartements offrent 2 chambres et 2 salles de bains, tous avec des terrasses spacieuses pour profiter de l'air frais, des vues et du climat méditerranéen. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Apartamenty posiadają 2 sypialnie i 2 łazienki, a także przestronne tarasy, które pozwalają cieszyć się świeżym powietrzem, widokami i śródziemnomorskim klimatem. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji. ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178930ea3666f178930ea73.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17894e74a766f17894e74e4.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178989eb2466f178989eb62.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu6ln5e3f1nk817tk15ll1ec41g.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i8fkea281af9kacbhvb3ftjv1g.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1789e3437e66f1789e343bb.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1789ff1ff666f1789ff2034.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178a1c329266f178a1c32ce.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178a389ac166f178a389afe.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178a5594b566f178a5594f2.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178a7279ad66f178a7279ea.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1789a712fe66f1789a7133b.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f178a8ec0ef66f178a8ec12d.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1789c4f50466f1789c4f541.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>504</id>
<date>2025-08-27 10:31:50</date>
<ref>628</ref>
<price>445000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>3</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>103</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/504/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The apartments have 3 bedrooms and 2 bathrooms, all with spacious terraces to enjoy the fresh air, the views and the Mediterranean climate. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Los apartamentos ofrecen 3 dormitorios y 2 baños, todos con terrazas espaciosas para disfrutar del aire libre, las vistas y el clima mediterránea. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De appartementen bieden 3 slaapkamers en 2 badkamers, met ruime terrassen om te genieten van de frisse lucht, het uitzicht en het mediterrane klimaat. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen. , alsook een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les appartements offrent 3 chambres et 2 salles de bains, tous avec des terrasses spacieuses pour profiter de l'air frais, des vues et du climat méditerranéen. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój,&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Apartamenty posiadają 3 sypialnie i 2 łazienki, a także przestronne tarasy, które pozwalają cieszyć się świeżym powietrzem, widokami i śródziemnomorskim klimatem. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji. ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c13013f766f17c1301435.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu7lpj1u9u1n7e1ortic11ujj1g.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c14d55a266f17c14d55e0.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c188402666f17c188407f.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c16b49dd66f17c16b4a1c.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c062b6e266f17c062b71f.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c07eff4e66f17c07eff9e.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c09c55b466f17c09c55f1.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c0d7186b66f17c0d718a8.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c0b9f53c66f17c0b9f579.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c0289d5b66f17c0289d98.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c0f3c51f66f17c0f3c55b.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c04594db66f17c0459537.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17c111c0a966f17c111c0e7.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>505</id>
<date>2025-07-22 15:21:57</date>
<ref>629</ref>
<price>485000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>80</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/505/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The penthouses stand out for their private solarium, accessed via a private staircase from the main terrace. From here, you can enjoy breathtaking views of the sea and the iconic Benidorm skyline. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Los áticos destacan por su solárium privado, al que se accede por una escalera privada desde la terraza principal. Desde aquí, podrás disfrutar de impresionantes vistas al mar y al icónico skyline de Benidorm. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De penthouses beschikken over een privésolarium, bereikbaar via een private trap vanaf het hoofdterras. Vanaf hier heb je een adembenemend uitzicht op zee en de iconische skyline van Benidorm. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen. , alsook een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les penthouses se distinguent par leur solarium privé, auquel on accède par un escalier privé depuis la terrasse principale. De là, vous pouvez profiter d'une vue imprenable sur la mer et sur l'horizon emblématique de Benidorm. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Penthouse'y wyróżniają się prywatnym solarium, do którego prowadzą prywatne schody z głównego tarasu. Stąd można podziwiać zapierające dech w piersiach widoki na morze oraz ikoniczną panoramę Benidorm. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Solarium</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Solar panels</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d69d5ae666f17d69d5b22.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d680c49c66f17d680c4d8.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d6d8d1ab66f17d6d8d1dc.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu8t0v7ajd2d1oi4169s1fgt1m.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d5b487e166f17d5b4881f.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d5d1b8b466f17d5d1b8f2.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d5ee52af66f17d5ee52ec.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d627ac6e66f17d627acab.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d60ab4e866f17d60ab525.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d57a389666f17d57a38d4.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu8t0v1aql1rjp42a1prvph71j.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu8t0vnsn1pelk5pfv3mgn1k.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tu8t0v6e5bdrqis71dhd1l.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d644452066f17d644455e.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d59746a166f17d59746e3.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f17d662bb4366f17d662bb7f.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>506</id>
<date>2025-07-24 12:52:54</date>
<ref>630</ref>
<price>575000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>3</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>103</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/506/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The penthouses stand out for their private solarium, accessed via a private staircase from the main terrace. From here, you can enjoy breathtaking views of the sea and the iconic Benidorm skyline. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Los áticos destacan por su solárium privado, al que se accede por una escalera privada desde la terraza principal. Desde aquí, podrás disfrutar de impresionantes vistas al mar y al icónico skyline de Benidorm. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De penthouses beschikken over een privésolarium, bereikbaar via een private trap vanaf het hoofdterras. Vanaf hier heb je een adembenemend uitzicht op zee en de iconische skyline van Benidorm. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en een berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen, alsook een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les penthouses se distinguent par leur solarium privé, auquel on accède par un escalier privé depuis la terrasse principale. De là, vous pouvez profiter d'une vue imprenable sur la mer et sur l'horizon emblématique de Benidorm. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój,&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Penthouse'y wyróżniają się prywatnym solarium, do którego prowadzą prywatne schody z głównego tarasu. Stąd można podziwiać zapierające dech w piersiach widoki na morze oraz ikoniczną panoramę Benidorm. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Solarium</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Solar panels</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tuahtp1uin126a1v4e103412u11m.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1830fe7a2c66f1830fe7a73.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f18311c929966f18311c92ce.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1830e1531f66f1830e15365.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1831ea4dad66f1831ea4dea.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f183207148d66f18320714cb.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f183177a3a766f183177a3e6.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1831b127ab66f1831b127e8.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1831945ac466f1831945b03.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f183224197466f18322419b2.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tuahtp2ibc7c6ftj8iaki1j.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tuahtp1ntb1vcj1cml19i2ku61k.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/o_1i9tuahtp17fp1v5p18s61kthhfs1l.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f18313aaa2066f18313aaa5d.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f1831cd1e6266f1831cd1eba.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d66f18315892be66f18315892fc.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>627</id>
<date>2025-07-22 15:46:38</date>
<ref>745</ref>
<price>515000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>3</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>103</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/627/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The ground floor properties have generous private gardens ranging. These green areas offer direct access to the swimming pool and communal areas, creating a perfect space to relax and enjoy the surroundings to the full.&amp;nbsp; Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las viviendas en planta baja cuentan con generosos jardines privados. Estas áreas verdes ofrecen acceso directo a la piscina y a las zonas comunes, creando un espacio perfecto para relajarse y disfrutar al máximo del entorno. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De appartementen op de begane grond hebben een privétuin. Deze tuinen bieden directe toegang tot het zwembad en de gemeenschappelijke ruimtes, waardoor een ideale plek ontstaat om te ontspannen en van de omgeving te genieten. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen. Er is tevens een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les appartements du rez-de-chaussée disposent de généreux jardins privés. Ces espaces verts offrent un accès direct à la piscine et aux espaces communs, créant ainsi un endroit idéal pour se détendre et profiter pleinement de l'environnement. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w Finestrat Paradise Resort są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój, Finestrat Paradise Resort oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Nieruchomości na parterze posiadają przestronne prywatne ogrody. Te zielone przestrzenie zapewniają bezpośredni dostęp do basenu i stref wspólnych, tworząc idealne miejsce do relaksu i pełnego korzystania z otoczenia. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Garden</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f94a375de3687f94a375e21.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f949dd6192687f949dd61e1.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f94a191a7d687f94a191ab9.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f949821143687f949821182.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f949fb69ae687f949fb6a0c.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f9492872b5687f9492872fa.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f94946207d687f9494620c0.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f94963573e687f94963577f.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f948ebad0a687f948ebad54.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f9490a545a687f9490a5499.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f948addd81687f948adddc1.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f9499e9a9b687f9499e9ad8.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f948cb4167687f948cb41a5.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d687f949bec350687f949bec396.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
<property>
<id>636</id>
<date>2025-08-04 09:49:27</date>
<ref>754</ref>
<price>595000</price>
<currency>EUR</currency>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<new_build>1</new_build>
<type>
<![CDATA[ Apartment ]]>
</type>
<town>Finestrat</town>
<province>Costa Blanca North</province>
<location_detail>Finestrat</location_detail>
<beds>3</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<location>
<latitude>38.543569</latitude>
<longitude>-0.185054</longitude>
</location>
<surface_area>
<built>103</built>
</surface_area>
<url>
<en>https://silcestates.com/property/636/apartment/in-construction/spain/costa-blanca-north/finestrat/finestrat/</en>
</url>
<desc>
<en>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is an exclusive residential complex consisting of 66 apartments and 14 villas, situated in a privileged location in Finestrat. Just a few minutes from the stunning beaches of Benidorm, surrounded by shopping centres, luxury hotels, golf courses and a wide range of leisure activities, this resort is ideal for those looking for quality of life and comfort.&#13;&#13; Each property has been designed to offer maximum privacy, with large sea-facing terraces, private gardens on the ground floors and solariums on the upper floors.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The complex has extensive resort-style communal areas, including swimming pools, gymnasium, coworking areas, sports facilities and green spaces, designed for relaxation and enjoyment of the natural surroundings.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The villas of Finestrat Paradise Resort are fully integrated into the residential complex, with access to all the services and amenities of the resort.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Committed to sustainability, Finestrat Paradise Resort has properties with high energy efficiency, with A classification and various ecological measures that not only care for the environment, but also allow significant savings in household expense.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; The penthouses stand out for their private solarium, accessed via a private staircase from the main terrace. From here, you can enjoy breathtaking views of the sea and the iconic Benidorm skyline. Each apartment comes with one parking space and one storage room in the underground car park, included in the price and the complex comes with a parking area for bicycles.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prices subject to availability. Contact us for more information.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</en>
<es>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort es un exclusivo complejo residencial compuesto por 66 apartamentos y 14 villas, situado en una ubicación privilegiada en Finestrat. A pocos minutos de las impresionantes playas de Benidorm, rodeado de centros comerciales, hoteles de lujo, campos de golf y una amplia oferta de ocio, este resort es ideal para quienes buscan calidad de vida y comodidad.&#13;&#13; Cada vivienda ha sido diseñada para ofrecer la máxima privacidad, con amplias terrazas orientadas al mar, jardines privados en las plantas bajas y solárium en las plantas superiores.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; El complejo cuenta con extensas zonas comunes de estilo resort, que incluyen piscinas, gimnasio, áreas de coworking, instalaciones deportivas y espacios verdes, pensados para el relax y el disfrute de su entorno natural.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Las villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort se integran completamente en el residencial, con acceso a todos los servicios y comodidades del complejo.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Comprometido con la sostenibilidad, Finestrat Paradise Resort cuenta con viviendas de alta eficiencia energética, con clasificación A y diversas medidas ecológicas que no solo cuidan el medio ambiente, sino que también permiten un ahorro significativo en los gastos del hogar.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Los áticos destacan por su solárium privado, al que se accede por una escalera privada desde la terraza principal. Desde aquí, podrás disfrutar de impresionantes vistas al mar y al icónico skyline de Benidorm. Cada apartamento viene con una plaza de parking y 1 trastero en el parking subterráneo, incluido en el precio y el complejo viene con zona de aparcamiento para bicicletas.&#13;&#13; Precios sujetos a disponibilidad. Póngase en contacto con nosotros para más información. ]]>
</es>
<nl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort is een exclusief wooncomplex met 66 appartementen en 14 villa's, gelegen op een unieke locatie in Finestrat. Slechts enkele minuten verwijderd van de prachtige stranden van Benidorm, en omringd door winkelcentra, luxe hotels, golfbanen en tal van recreatieve activiteiten. Dit resort is ideaal voor wie op zoek is naar kwaliteit en comfort in het leven.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Elke woning is ontworpen om maximale privacy te bieden, ruime terrassen (sommige) met zeezicht, privétuinen op de begane grond en solariums op de bovenste verdiepingen.&#13;&#13; Het complex beschikt over uitgebreide gemeenschappelijke ruimtes in resortstijl, waaronder zwembaden, een fitnessruimte, coworking-ruimtes, sportfaciliteiten en groene zones, ontworpen om te ontspannen en te genieten van de natuurlijke omgeving.&#13;&#13; De villa's van Finestrat Paradise Resort zijn volledig geïntegreerd in het wooncomplex, met toegang tot alle faciliteiten en voorzieningen van het resort.&#13;&#13; Toegewijd aan duurzaamheid, biedt Finestrat Paradise Resort woningen met hoge energie-efficiëntie (klasse A), met diverse ecologische maatregelen die niet alleen het milieu beschermen, maar ook aanzienlijke besparingen op de woonlasten mogelijk maken.&#13;&#13; De penthouses beschikken over een privésolarium, bereikbaar via een private trap vanaf het hoofdterras. Vanaf hier heb je een adembenemend uitzicht op zee en de iconische skyline van Benidorm. Een ondergrondse parkeerplaats en een berging zijn tevens in de prijs inbegrepen, alsook een gemeenschappelijke fietsenstalling.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Prijzen onder voorbehoud van beschikbaarheid. Neem contact met ons op voor meer informatie.&#13;&#13; ]]>
</nl>
<fr>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort est un complexe résidentiel exclusif comprenant 66 appartements et 14 villas, situé dans un endroit privilégié à Finestrat. À quelques minutes des magnifiques plages de Benidorm, entouré de centres commerciaux, d'hôtels de luxe, de terrains de golf et d'un large éventail d'activités de loisirs, ce complexe est idéal pour ceux qui recherchent la qualité de vie et le confort.&#13;&#13; Chaque propriété a été conçue pour offrir un maximum d'intimité, avec de grandes terrasses orientées vers la mer, des jardins privés au rez-de-chaussée et des solariums aux étages supérieurs.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Le complexe dispose de vastes espaces communs de style complexe, comprenant des piscines, un gymnase, des espaces de travail, des installations sportives et des espaces verts, conçus pour se détendre et profiter de la nature environnante.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Les villas de Finestrat Paradise Resort sont entièrement intégrées au complexe résidentiel, avec accès à tous les services et équipements du complexe.&#13;&#13; &#13;&#13; Engagé dans le développement durable, Finestrat Paradise Resort dispose de maisons à haute efficacité énergétique, classées A et dotées de diverses mesures écologiques qui non seulement protègent l'environnement, mais permettent également de réaliser des économies significatives sur les dépenses domestiques.&#13;&#13; Les penthouses se distinguent par leur solarium privé, auquel on accède par un escalier privé depuis la terrasse principale. De là, vous pouvez profiter d'une vue imprenable sur la mer et sur l'horizon emblématique de Benidorm. Chaque appartement dispose d'une places de stationnement et d’un débarras dans le parking souterrain, inclus dans le prix et le complexe dispose d'un parking à vélos.&amp;nbsp;&#13;&#13; Les prix sont soumis à disponibilité. Veuillez nous contacter pour plus d'informations. ]]>
</fr>
<pl>
<![CDATA[ Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;to ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkalny składający się z 66 apartamentów i 14 willi, położony w uprzywilejowanej lokalizacji w Finestrat. Zaledwie kilka minut od zachwycających plaż Benidorm, otoczony centrami handlowymi, luksusowymi hotelami, polami golfowymi oraz szeroką gamą atrakcji rekreacyjnych, ten resort jest idealnym wyborem dla osób poszukujących wysokiej jakości życia i komfortu.&#13;&#13; Każda nieruchomość została zaprojektowana z myślą o maksymalnej prywatności, oferując duże tarasy z widokiem na morze, prywatne ogrody na parterze oraz solaria na najwyższych piętrach.&#13;&#13; Kompleks dysponuje rozległymi wspólnymi strefami w stylu resortu, w tym basenami, siłownią, przestrzeniami do coworkingu, obiektami sportowymi oraz terenami zielonymi, które sprzyjają relaksowi i cieszeniu się naturalnym otoczeniem.&#13;&#13; Wille w&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;są w pełni zintegrowane z kompleksem mieszkalnym i mają dostęp do wszystkich usług oraz udogodnień resortu.&#13;&#13; Dbając o zrównoważony rozwój,&amp;nbsp;Finestrat Paradise Resort&amp;nbsp;oferuje nieruchomości o wysokiej efektywności energetycznej z klasą A oraz różnymi ekologicznymi rozwiązaniami, które nie tylko chronią środowisko, ale również pozwalają na znaczne oszczędności w kosztach eksploatacji.&#13;&#13; Penthouse'y wyróżniają się prywatnym solarium, do którego prowadzą prywatne schody z głównego tarasu. Stąd można podziwiać zapierające dech w piersiach widoki na morze oraz ikoniczną panoramę Benidorm. Każdy apartament obejmuje jedno miejsce parkingowe oraz komórkę lokatorską w podziemnym parkingu, wliczone w cenę. Dodatkowo kompleks oferuje strefę parkingową dla rowerów.&#13;&#13; Ceny zależą od dostępności. Skontaktuj się z nami, aby uzyskać więcej informacji. ]]>
</pl>
</desc>
<features>
<feature>Air conditioning</feature>
<feature>Lift</feature>
<feature>Home appliances</feature>
<feature>Communal swimming pool</feature>
<feature>Reinforced door</feature>
<feature>Solarium</feature>
<feature>Terrace</feature>
<feature>Storage room</feature>
<feature>Underfloor heating in bathrooms</feature>
<feature>Domotics system</feature>
<feature>Aerothermal system</feature>
<feature>Alarm</feature>
<feature>Solar panels</feature>
<feature>Built-in wardrobes</feature>
<feature>Electric shutters</feature>
</features>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064f181db7689064f181df4.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064fcb296d689064fcb29aa.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064efa21bb689064efa21fa.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064edca80a689064edca849.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e26946a689064e2694a7.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064f3749f0689064f374a2e.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e44c2eb689064e44c32c.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e805c50689064e805c90.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e631d9d689064e631e23.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064f5554ab689064f5554f1.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064f72d0f1689064f72d12f.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064f911b7a689064f911bbb.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064fadfec7689064fadff02.JPG</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e9cecb1689064e9cecf0.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064e085084689064e0850c6.jpg</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>https://silcestates.com/media/images/properties/d689064ebc1097689064ebc10f7.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
<virtual_tour_url>https://my.matterport.com/show/?m=BTsEgim14pz</virtual_tour_url>
</property>
</root>